

# Tim Hsu

### Address: 3/F Flat D. 18-26 Portland Street. Yau Ma Tei. Kowloon, HK.

## **Yee Feng Hsu**

徐宇鈞

http://yeehsu.freeshell.org zaken520@gmail.com (852) 9273-7829

#### **Profile**

Worked in software development for 15+ years. Started in Silicon Valley, then moved to HK. Majority time was a C++ developer but recently moved to C# .NET. Consider myself a Fullstack developer with some frontend knowledge. Very good with design patterns, algorithms, web apps, Fintech, and Blockchain.

Certified SCRUM Master using Agile methodology, CI/CD, and Test Driven Development.

#### **Education**

San Francisco State University - B.S. Computer Science. 2002.

#### **Technical Skills**

C/C++	C# .NET
OOP & Design Patterns	Data Structures & Algorithms
Agile, CI/CD, TDD	SCRUM
MySQL, Store Procedures	MSSQL, T-SQL
TCP/IP Sockets	IPC & Multi-threading
HTML5, CSS3, JS	Web 2.0
Windows Services, WCF, MVC	Linux, Bash

#### **Professional Working History**

#### **Avanade**

Senior .NET Consultant

November 2017 - Present

Quarry Bay, Hong Kong

- Provided .NET consultancy to various fortune 500 clients, including Accenture
- Used C# Web API 2.0, MVC, Message Queue, Asynchronous calls, MSSQL, MSUnit
- · Worked in Agile/SCRUM methods including CI/CD, TDD, BDD, SpecFlow, refactoring
- Helped in DevOps, releases, Jenkins, JIRA, Confluence, Selenium, Microsoft 365 dynamics

#### **Concord Pacific Satellite Technologies Ltd.**

November 2015 - June 2017

#### Lead Analyst Programmer

Kowloon, Hong Kong

- Lead cross-regional Agile team to develop GPS Fleet Management SAAS solution
- Lead front-end development team using Javascript, JQuery, AngularJS, JSON, Bootstrap
- Revamped SOA backend using C# .NET, MySQL, TCP/IP sockets, threads, SOAP & WCF APIs
- Introduced to team: Agile, TDD, NUnit, MantisBT, SVN, GIT, Skype, Google Maps

#### **Global Talent Services Ltd. - Unisys Hong Kong Ltd.**

January 2015 - November 2015

#### Contrator / Developer

Kwun Tong, Hong Kong

- Independant contractor implemented banking Signature Web Viewer Verification system
- Fullstack using VB/C# .NET, WCF, HTML5, CSS3, AngularJS, JQuery, AJAX, REST, MSSQL
- Part of full SDLC in various phases, staging, SIT, UAT, then LIVE

#### **Sungard Global Trading Ltd.**

August 2011 - December 2014

#### Software Engineer

Central, Hong Kong

- Participated in development of real-time trading platform in WIN32 C++
- · Worked with various teams OMS, FIX, Market Data, Market Access, and Exchange PMs
- Debugged trading algorithms, strategies on cash, equities and derivative market
- Cross functional teams using Agile, TDD, and daily SCRUM to meet sprint targets

#### **QVIVO Ltd.**

Sr. Software Engineer

October 2010 - August 2011

Sheung Wan, Hong Kong

- Developed cross platform media player in standard C++/STL, Boost library, threads
- Integrated Facebook API, cURL, AWS Cloud, IPC and memory sharing libraries
- Used Agile, TDD, Google unit testing, FFMpeg, Scaleform GFX, DirectX, OpenGL

#### **Concord Pacific Satellite Technologies Ltd.**

November 2008 - October 2010

Sr. Software Engineer

Kowloon, Hong Kong

- Web Traffic & GPS related fleet management software control
- Embedded media player development using WinCE C++ MFC, WIN32, COM, HTTP, FTP
- Developed backend in C Linux, sockets, POSIX threads, MySQL tunning

#### **OPSWAT, Inc.**

April 2005 - October 2008

Sr. Software Engineer

San Francisco, USA

- Part of team to develop Antivirus/Antispyware/Firewall SDK
- Implemented API library in OOP C++, C#, Java, PHP, HTTP/FTP/SMTP, XML, STL
- Integrated computer security, encryption, hashing MD5, SHA256, digital signatures

#### One Share of Stock, Inc.

August 2003 - July 2004

SEO Specialist

San Francisco, USA

- Search Engine Optimization to place within Top-10 on Google and Yahoo
- Developed website using ASP/VBS, HTML/CSS/JavaScript and SQL
- Managed Webtrends, Linux, Bash scripts, SQL Servers and Apache

#### Mendocino. San Francisco Sales, Inc.

August 2002 - August 2003

Web Developer

San Francisco, USA

- Designed intranet using HTML, JS, CGI, XML/XSLT, and Photoshop
- Engineered inventory management & ERP system

#### Club-i - Cyber cafe

May 1998 - September 1998

Web Developer (Internship)

San Francisco, USA

- Designed intranet using HTML, JS, CGI, and Photoshop
- · Assisted customers on using PC, email, web browsers, printing